<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simple Shit.</title>
    <link>/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Simple Shit.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 13:32:40 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About Shit</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 13:32:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Don’t ever play yourself. Bless up. Learning is cool, but knowing is better, and I know the key to success. You do know, you do know that they don’t want you to have lunch. I’m keeping it real with you, so what you going do is have lunch. Don’t ever play yourself. We don’t see them, we will never see them. The key to more success is to have a lot of pillows. You should never complain, complaining is a weak emotion, you got life, we breathing, we blessed. To be successful you’ve got to work hard, to make history, simple, you’ve got to make it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In life there will be road blocks but we will over come it. They don’t want us to win. Let me be clear, you have to make it through the jungle to make it to paradise, that’s the key, Lion! A major key, never panic. Don’t panic, when it gets crazy and rough, don’t panic, stay calm. You smart, you loyal, you a genius. To succeed you must believe. When you believe, you will succeed. You see the hedges, how I got it shaped up? It’s important to shape up your hedges, it’s like getting a haircut, stay fresh. They will try to close the door on you, just open it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me be clear, you have to make it through the jungle to make it to paradise, that’s the key, Lion! It’s important to use cocoa butter. It’s the key to more success, why not live smooth? Why live rough? The other day the grass was brown, now it’s green because I ain’t give up. Never surrender. Learning is cool, but knowing is better, and I know the key to success. I’m up to something. A major key, never panic. Don’t panic, when it gets crazy and rough, don’t panic, stay calm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A major key, never panic. Don’t panic, when it gets crazy and rough, don’t panic, stay calm. Surround yourself with angels. Don’t ever play yourself. In life you have to take the trash out, if you have trash in your life, take it out, throw it away, get rid of it, major key. You do know, you do know that they don’t want you to have lunch. I’m keeping it real with you, so what you going do is have lunch. You do know, you do know that they don’t want you to have lunch. I’m keeping it real with you, so what you going do is have lunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put it this way, it took me twenty five years to get these plants, twenty five years of blood sweat and tears, and I’m never giving up, I’m just getting started. Let me be clear, you have to make it through the jungle to make it to paradise, that’s the key, Lion! Surround yourself with angels, positive energy, beautiful people, beautiful souls, clean heart, angel. The key to more success is to get a massage once a week, very important, major key, cloth talk. The key to more success is to get a massage once a week, very important, major key, cloth talk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They never said winning was easy. Some people can’t handle success, I can. Learning is cool, but knowing is better, and I know the key to success. Fan luv. Fan luv. Major key, don’t fall for the trap, stay focused. It’s the ones closest to you that want to see you fail. Life is what you make it, so let’s make it. To be successful you’ve got to work hard, to make history, simple, you’ve got to make it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t ever play yourself. We don’t see them, we will never see them. Let me be clear, you have to make it through the jungle to make it to paradise, that’s the key, Lion! Congratulations, you played yourself. It’s on you how you want to live your life. Everyone has a choice. I pick my choice, squeaky clean. The weather is amazing, walk with me through the pathway of more success. Take this journey with me, Lion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ladies always say Khaled you smell good, I use no cologne. Cocoa butter is the key. In life there will be road blocks but we will over come it. Cloth talk. Learning is cool, but knowing is better, and I know the key to success. I told you all this before, when you have a swimming pool, do not use chlorine, use salt water, the healing, salt water is the healing. Eliptical talk. Put it this way, it took me twenty five years to get these plants, twenty five years of blood sweat and tears, and I’m never giving up, I’m just getting started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In life you have to take the trash out, if you have trash in your life, take it out, throw it away, get rid of it, major key. You do know, you do know that they don’t want you to have lunch. I’m keeping it real with you, so what you going do is have lunch. The first of the month is coming, we have to get money, we have no choice. It cost money to eat and they don’t want you to eat. Learning is cool, but knowing is better, and I know the key to success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m giving you cloth talk, cloth. Special cloth alert, cut from a special cloth. Let me be clear, you have to make it through the jungle to make it to paradise, that’s the key, Lion! Cloth talk. It’s on you how you want to live your life. Everyone has a choice. I pick my choice, squeaky clean. They don’t want us to eat. They don’t want us to win. The key to success is to keep your head above the water, never give up. They will try to close the door on you, just open it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life is shit learn to love it.</title>
      <link>/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 13:30:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You see that bamboo behind me though, you see that bamboo? Ain’t nothin’ like bamboo. Bless up. Let me be clear, you have to make it through the jungle to make it to paradise, that’s the key, Lion! The key to more success is to get a massage once a week, very important, major key, cloth talk. You see the hedges, how I got it shaped up? It’s important to shape up your hedges, it’s like getting a haircut, stay fresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Give thanks to the most high. Surround yourself with angels. Special cloth alert. It’s important to use cocoa butter. It’s the key to more success, why not live smooth? Why live rough? You see the hedges, how I got it shaped up? It’s important to shape up your hedges, it’s like getting a haircut, stay fresh. Let’s see what Chef Dee got that they don’t want us to eat. The weather is amazing, walk with me through the pathway of more success. Take this journey with me, Lion! I told you all this before, when you have a swimming pool, do not use chlorine, use salt water, the healing, salt water is the healing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch your back, but more importantly when you get out the shower, dry your back, it’s a cold world out there. Another one. The key to success is to keep your head above the water, never give up. Give thanks to the most high. They never said winning was easy. Some people can’t handle success, I can. Eliptical talk. Surround yourself with angels, positive energy, beautiful people, beautiful souls, clean heart, angel. Wraith talk. In life there will be road blocks but we will over come it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key to success is to keep your head above the water, never give up. Mogul talk. The key is to enjoy life, because they don’t want you to enjoy life. I promise you, they don’t want you to jetski, they don’t want you to smile. A major key, never panic. Don’t panic, when it gets crazy and rough, don’t panic, stay calm. Don’t ever play yourself. You see the hedges, how I got it shaped up? It’s important to shape up your hedges, it’s like getting a haircut, stay fresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Give thanks to the most high. To be successful you’ve got to work hard, to make history, simple, you’ve got to make it. How’s business? Boomin. The ladies always say Khaled you smell good, I use no cologne. Cocoa butter is the key. The key to more success is to have a lot of pillows. I’m giving you cloth talk, cloth. Special cloth alert, cut from a special cloth. In life there will be road blocks but we will over come it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>